<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="app_name">Genesis Chess Beta</string>
	<string name="version">1.9.2</string>
	<string name="register_notice">
		NOTICE: A valid email address must be used to activate the account.
	</string>
	<string name="register_activation">
		Your account\'s email address must be verified before logging in.
		An activation link has been sent to the email address used to register.\n\nPlease
		make sure that your spam filter doesn\'t block:\n\tactivation@genesischess.com
	</string>
	<string name="delete_local">
		Are you sure you want to delete this game? The game can not be recovered.
	</string>
	<string name="delete_archive">
		Are you sure you want to delete this archived game? The game will not be deleted from the server.
	</string>
	<string name="logout_confirm">
		Are you sure you want to logout of your account?
		Online games will be unavailable until you login.
	</string>
	<string name="register_confirm">
		Are you sure you want to register an account with the following information?
	</string>
	<string name="resign_confirm">
		Are you sure you want to resign from this game? You will lose PSR if this is a random game.
	</string>
	<string name="nudge_confirm">
		Are you sure you want to Nudge your opponent? This will email them and give them one week to move before you can close the game.
	</string>
	<string name="idleresign_confirm">
		Your opponent has been idle. Are you sure you want to force close the game?
	</string>
	<string name="copygame_confirm">
		Are you sure you want to make a local copy this game?
	</string>
	<string name="cputime_msg">
		Set the time alloted for the computer to think. Longer times makes the computer stronger.
	</string>
	<string name="feedback_url">
		https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?formkey=dEVMcnVvbDFMWkZ0azNyQ2hRR3RjZWc6MQ
	</string>
	<string name="gamepool_info">
		You are waiting to be matched with an opponent in the following game types:
	</string>
	<string name="readallmsgs">
		Are you sure you want to mark all messages as read?
	</string>
	<string name="deleteLocalTable">
		Are you sure you want to delete all local games? This operation can not be undone!
	</string>
	<string name="resyncOnlineTable">
		Are you sure you want to force a full resync of all active games?
	</string>
	<string name="resyncArchiveTable">
		Are you sure you want to force a full resync of all archive games?
	</string>
	<string name="resyncMsgTable">
		Are you sure you want to force a full resync of all game messages?
	</string>
</resources>
